Hmm, This cake is amazing
이 케익 죽인다!
세상에, 아예 모텔에 방을 잡아라
Oh, my god. Get a room
나 같으면 방 잡는다
I would get a room with this cake
이 케익에게 정말 즐거운 시간을
보내게 해줄 수 있을 것 같아
I think I show this cake a good time.
음식하고 섹스 중에서 하나를
포기해야 한다면 넌 뭘 포기할래?
If you had to, what would you give up-- food or sex?
섹스!
Sex.
대답 한번 정말 느리게 한다
Seriously, answer faster.
미안해, 근데 피비가 물어봤을 때
난 자기랑 섹스를 생각도 안했어
Oh, I'm sorry, honey. No, when she said sex, I wasn't thinking about sex with you.
모니카 대답은 따뜻한 포옹처럼
내 맘을 참 편하게 해
It's like a giant hug.
로스, 너는 어때?
음식하고 섹스 중에 뭘 포기할래?
Ross, how about you?
Which would you give up--sex or food?
음식
Food.
그러면, 섹스와 공룡 중에서는?
OK, uh, How about sex or dinosaurs?
세상에, 꼭 "소피의 선택" 같아
* 메릴 스트립 주연의 영화제목
Oh, my god. It's like sophie's choice.
조이, 너는 어때?
음식하고 섹스 중에서 뭘 포기할거야?
What about you, Joe?
What would you give up-- sex or food?
Uh... ooh... uh.
모르겠어, 너무 어려워
I don't know. It's too hard.
안돼, 하나 골라야 돼
No, you gotta pick one.
uh... food.
No, sex.
그럼.. 음식!
아니 섹스!
음식!
Food.
섹스!
Sex.
음식! 모르겠어
둘 다 원해, 난...
Food. Se... I don't know.
Oh, god, I want both.
I want... I want girls on bread.
난 여자 샌드위치를 원해
FㆍRㆍIㆍEㆍNㆍDㆍS
10x10 The One Where Chandler Gets Caught
[해 석]
이승훈(chandler7@korea.com)
[싱 커]
임욱재(sys_friends6@korea.com)
임의 수정 및 상업적용도의 사용을 금합니다
자막 피드백은 게시판을 이용해 주세요
(club.korea.com/friends)
Okay, you've got to see these latest pictures of Emma.
에마 사진 좀 봐봐
Oh, how cute. Oh, she looks just like a little doll.
정말 귀엽다, 꼭 인형 같아
아니야, 그건 진짜 인형이고
Oh, no, no. That is a doll.
Oh, thank god, 'cause that thing's really creepy.
다행이다
사실 이거 좀 징그러워
저기 봐, 챈들러다
Oh, there's Chandler.
Oh. Who's the blonde? She's pretty.
저 금발은 누구지? 예쁜데?
쟤 바람 피나봐!
He's having an affair.
쟤 바람 안피워
He is not having an affair.
이런 건 내가 항상
잘 찍는다는 거 알잖아
You know I'm always right about these things.
무슨 소리야, 넌 지난주엔
로스가 널 죽이려 한다고 그랬잖아!
No, you're not. Last week you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
아니, 사실 너도 믿기 힘들잖아
Well, I'm sorry, but it's hard to believe
세상에 누가 그런 일상적인 얘기하면서
그렇게 지루한 얘기를 하겠어
that anyone would tell a story that dull just to tell it.
I swear there's something going on with them. Look.
진짜, 저 둘 사이에 뭔가가 있다니까!
봐봐, 챈들러가 저 여자 차를 타잖아!
He's getting into the car with her.
그건 아무 의미도 없어!
Oh, that doesn't mean anything.
그래? 이러면 어떻게 되는지 보자
Oh, yeah? Well, let's see.
Huh?
밑으로 숙여!
Okay, duck down.
Oh.
여보세요?
Hello.
챈들러, 나 피빈데
오늘 모니카 일하니까
Oh, hi, Chandler, it's phoebe.
I know that Monica is working today
so I was wondering if you wanted to come to the movies with me and rachel.
너 혹시 나랑 레이첼이랑
영화보러 갈래?
아, 오늘 나도 일해야 돼
Oh, uh... I have to work, too.
Yeah, I'm stuck here at the office all day.
하루종일 사무실에서
꼼짝없이 갇혀있어야 돼
Uh, well, it's a shame that you'll,
that you'll miss the movie
'cause we were gonna see, you know, either,
그래? 영화보러 못간다니까 아쉽네
특히나 우리가 보러갈려고 했던게..
um, liar, liar or,
"라이어 라이어"나..
"배신"이나..
... betrayal or
"어페어 투 리멤버"거든
an affair to remember.
그 영화들 전부 개봉한지
오래된 것들이잖아?
Those are all really old.
알았어, 그렇다면..
Okay, then maybe it'll be, um...
"내 차 봤냐?" 보러 간다고 그래
Dude, where's my car?
- 뭐?!
- 쟤네들 차 안에 있잖아
What?
They're in a car.
알았어, 이따 얘기하자
안녕~
Okay, well, all right, talk to you later.
Okay, bye. Okay, quick.
좋아, 서둘러
우리 택시 잡아타고 쫓아가야돼
We got to find a cab and follow them.
무슨 수색작전도 아니고, 그럴거면
야간투시경이랑 스턴건도 가져가지
Oh, yeah, okay,
Let me just grab my night-vision goggles and my stun gun.
나 그거 있어
I got 'em.
- 안녕
- 안녕, 자기야
Hey.
Hey. Hey, sweetie.
Hey you smell like perfume and cigarettes.
자기한테서 향수랑 담배냄새 나는데?
하루 종일 낸시의 차에 있었잖아
I was in the car with Nancy all day.
낸시는 담배 안피워
Nancy doesn't smoke.
그래? 최소한 향수는
내꺼 아니니깐 그거에나 감사해
Well, at least the perfume's not mine.
Be thankful for that.
So?
그건 그렇고..
그 집 가보니까 어때?
What did you think of the house?
완벽해! 우리가 찾던
모든 걸 갖추고 있어
It's perfect. It's everything we've been looking for.
그치? 정말 환상적인 웨인스코딩에
크라운몰딩에 다락방의 지붕창이랑..
Isn't it? And what about the, the amazing wainscoting
and the crown molding and the dormer windows in the attic?
그리고 어쩌구랑 저쩌구랑도..
And the wigglewoms and the zipzorps?
네가 말한게 뭐였지?
What were the things you said?
그 큰 마당도 좋지 않아?
Don't you love the huge yard?
침실의 벽난로도
And the fireplace in the bedroom.
그리고 낸시가 그러는데
And Nancy said it's really under-priced
그 사람이 직장에서 쫓겨나 다시
부모님과 살게돼서 그렇게 싼거래
because the guy lost his job and has to move in with his parents.
정말 너의 착한 본성을 드러내는구나
This is bringing out a lovely color in you.
우리가 그 집을 사는게 맞는 거 같아?
So... do you think we should get it?
모르겠어, 너는?
I don't know. What do you think?
- 사야 될 거 같아
- 나도
I think we should.
I do, too.
This is huge.
I know.
- 이건 중요한 일이야
- 나도 알아
지금 어때?
담배 피우고 싶어지지 않아?
How bad do you want to smoke right now?
담배 같은 거 안해..
이 말하는 거대한 담배야
I don't know what you mean...giant talking cigarette.
그리고 내가 낸시 차에 타려는데
피비가 전화했어
Oh, by the way, phoebe called just
as I was getting into nancy's car,
so if she asks you,
I was at work all day.
Gotcha.
- 그래서 종일 직장에서 일한다고 했어
- 말 뜻 이해했어
언제 이 얘기를 다른 애들한테 하지?
When do we tell them about this?
100% 확실하기 전까진 안하는거야
아직 확실치도 않은데 왜 실망시켜?
We don't. Not until it's a hundred percent.
Why upset everybody over nothing?
맞아, 걔네한테 말하기
너무 힘들 것 같아
Okay. Right.
Oh, my god, that is going to be so hard.
그러게
I know. Good luck with it.
넌 잘할 테니까, 네가 해
챈들러가 바람을 핀다니
믿을 수가 없어
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
확실해
우리가 웨스트체스터까지 따라갔는데
I'm telling you guys, we followed them out to a house in westchester.
집에 들어가 45분쯤 있다가 나오는데
매우 기분좋아 보였다니까
They went in for like 45 minutes and then they came out looking pretty happy.
챈들러가?
Chandler?
45분이나?
45 minutes?
절대 그럴 리가 없어
Well, something's not right.
난 챈들러가 모니카에게
그런 짓을 했다는게 안믿겨
I just can't believe he would do this to monica.
그러게 말야..
게다가 이제 애도 올텐데
I know and, and with the baby coming.
- 그럼 우린 모니카에게 말해줘야하나?
- 모르겠어
So, should we tell her? I don't know.
만약 마이크가 다른 여자랑 있는걸
봤다면 넌 우리가 말해주기를 원해?
Phoebe, if, if one of us saw mike with another woman, would you want us to tell you?
왜, 너 마이크가
다른 여자랑 있는 거 봤어?
Why, who'd you see him with?
그건 아니고
그냥, 만약에 우리가..
No one. I'm just saying, if we...
아는 대로 말해!
tell me what you know!
아니야, 그런 거 없어, 마이크는
좋은 사람이고 그냥 가정해 본 거야
wow. No, nothing. Mike's a great guy. It was hypothetical.
All right. He is a good guy.
그 사람은 그럴 리 없지..
네 말이 맞아
마이크가 바람을 피울 리 없어
You're right. He wouldn't cheat.
마이크가 다른 여자랑 있는 걸
봤다 하더라도, 나 같으면..
Believe me, if I did see him with someone,
there's no way I...
그 여자 누구였냐니깐!
Who did you see him with?!
Oh, look at her. So happy.
모니카 좀 봐..
정말 행복해 보이잖아
Oh, look at her. So happy.
이 청소기를 청소할 더 작은
청소기가 있다면 얼마나 좋아
If only there were a smaller one to clean this one.
지금 챈들러 여기 있어?
Hey, is, uh, is-is chandler here?
아니, 저녁 찾으러 갔어
왜, 무슨 일 있어?
No, he's picking up dinner. Why, what's up?
Well... look, whatever happens, we're here for you, and we love you.
무슨 일이 일어나든 간에
우린 네 곁에 있고, 널 사랑해
- 그래서?
- 챈들러가 바람피는거 같아
All right.
We think chandler might be having an affair.
뭐라구?
What?
챈들러가 금발 여자와 같이 있는 걸
피비랑 내가 오늘 봤어
Phoebe and I saw chandler with a blonde woman today outside on the street and then
우리가 웨스트체스터에 있는
집까지 쫓아가봤는데..
we followed them to a house in westchester.
둘이 같이 안으로 들어가더라..
미안해
They went in together.
So sorry.
오 세상에..
이런 끔찍한 일이..
Oh, my god. Oh, my god, that's awful.
그 집 어땠어?
What did you think of the house?
뭐라고?
What?
- 모니카, 우리 말 뜻은 이해한거지?
- 그래, 이해했어
Monica, you understand what we are saying, right?
Yea, sure.
I'm devastated, obviously.
당연히 난 지금 충격을 받았지
그 동네가 자기 집처럼
매우 안락하다는 생각은 들어?
Did you think neighgorhood is homey?
안녕?
Hey.
이런 망할 자식
You son of a bitch.
내가 이상한거야, 아님 이제 우리도
지옥에서 쓰는 말로 인사하기로 한거야?
Is it me or the greeting is gone down hell around here?
피비와 레이첼이 오늘
자기가 낸시랑 있는 걸 보고
Pheobe and Rachel saw you with Nancy today
and they think you are having an affair.
자기가 바람을 피운다고 생각해
- 낸시가 누구야?
- 어떻게 된 일이야?
Who's nancy?
What's going on?
Uh... okay.
All right, guys, you better sit down.
This is, this is pretty big.
좋아.. 중요한 얘기니까
다들 앉는게 좋겠다
난 바람피는게 아냐
I'm not having an affair.
낸시는 우리 공인중개인이야
Nancy... is our realtor.
내가 뭐랬어, 챈들러가 여자랑
45분간이나 했을리가 없댔잖아
I knew he couldn't be with a woman for 45 minutes!
I knew it. I knew it.
Why... w-why do you have a realtor?
왠 공인중개인?
Um... she's been showing us houses outside of the city.
교외에 있는 집을 알아봐 주고 있어
뭐라구?
What?
그게 정말이야?
Are you serious?
우리가 아이 입양 결정된 후에
챈들러와 내가 얘기를 해봤는데
When we found out that we were going to get this baby,
Chandler and I started talking and we decided
that we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.
우리는 도시에서 아이를
기르고 싶지 않다고 결론을 내렸어
그래서.. 이사갈 거야?
So you're, so you're gonna move?
맙소사..
Oh, my god.
이런 문제 결정할 때는 최소한
투표라도 해야 되는 거 아니야?
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
도시에서 애 키우는 게 어때서 그래?
What is wrong with raising a kid in the city?
나도 키우고.. 로스도 키우고..
I'm doing it. Ross is doing it.
사라 제시카 파커 도 키우는데!
* '섹스 앤 더 시티'의 주연여배우
Sarah Jessica Parker is doing it.
너희들한테는 좋을지 모르지만..
And that's great for you guys,
우리는 잔디밭 마당과
현관 앞 그네를 원해
but we want a lawn and a swing set.
또 애들이 자전거 타며 놀수 있고
아이스크림차가 다니는 거리에서 살고 싶어
And a street where our kids can ride their bikes
and maybe an ice cream truck can go by.
그러려면 1950년대의 집을 사야지
So you want to buy a house in the '50s.
너희가 무엇을 포기해야 하는지
생각해 봤어?
Have you thought about what you're giving up?
도시 밖으로 이사가면 못하는 것들..
You can't move out of the city.
What if... what if you want chinese food at 5:00 A.M.?
새벽 5시에 중국집 음식이
먹고 싶으면 어떻게 할 거야?
아니면 비오면 바로 고장나는
가짜 롤렉스 시계가 갖고 싶다면?
Or a fake rolex that breaks as soon as it rains?
아니면 문 앞까지 배달되는
동양인 창녀를 원할땐 어떻게 하게?
Or an asian hooker sent right to your door?
있잖아, 도시 밖에서 집을 찾고 싶다면..
그렇게 해
You know what?
If you want to look for a house, that's okay.
아니야, 절대 괜찮지 않아
얘 말 듣지 마, 너 한대 맞는다
No, no, it's not.
Don't listen to him.
I'm gonna thump you.
괜찮아, 왜냐하면 도시 밖에서는
살 수 없다고 깨달을 테니까
It's okay because they have to get it out of their system.
Okay? But, you're gonna realize,
this is the only place you want to be.
그러면 이곳이 최고라는 걸
알게 될 거야
사실, 벌써 우리는 맘에
쏙 드는 집을 찾았어
Actually... we already found a house we love.
뭐?
What?
그리고 한시간쯤 전에 우리가
사겠다고 하고 금액을 제시했어
And about an hour ago, we made an offer.
이쯤 되니까 내가 바람 피웠으면
차라리 더 나았을 것 같지?
Bet you wish I was having an affair now, huh?
집을 살 금액을 제시했다고?
You put an offer on a house?
얼마나 좋은데..
시냇가로 이어지는 큰 마당이 있고..
It has this big yard that leads down to this stream.
또 커다란 단풍나무들이 있는데..
And then there's these old maple trees.
또 자연경관 얘기
너희가 비버라도 되니?
Oh, again with the nature!
What are you, beavers?
힘든 일인지 알아
그리고 그래서 우리는 정말 미안해
Look, I know this is really hard, and we're really sorry.
Is this because I come over here
without knocking and eat your food?
Because I can stop doing that.
내가 여기 와서 음식 집어먹는거
때문이라면 이제 더이상 안그럴게
I... I really, really think I can.
맘만 독하게 먹으면 할 수 있을거야
그게 이유가 아닌란걸 잘 알잖아
You know that's not the reason, Joe.
너희들도 그 집을 봤다면
우릴 이해하게 될거야
I think if you saw it, you'd understand.
너희는 가봤잖아
정말 아름답지 않아?
I mean, you guys were there.
It's-it's beautiful, isn't it?
사실 그건 그래
Yeah, it is.
- 지금 도대체 뭐하는 거야?
- 사실이 그래..
What the hell are you doing?!
Well... it is, all right?
우리가 오늘 그 앞에서 있는데
챈들러가 바람피운다는건 안믿겼지만
When we were out there today,
all I keep thinking was,
I can't believe Chandler is screwing this woman,
정말 예쁜 집이다라는 생각 밖에
안 들었다니까
but man, this would be a nice place to live!
그건 그래도..
Yeah, but so is this.
그래, 이사를 간다는 건
여기를 떠난다는 거야
Yeah, I mean, if you move ther you have to leave here.
어떻게 여길 떠날 수 있어?
I mean, how can you leave this place?
[Episode 101] 아빠, 제 말 좀 들어 보세요!
Come on, daddy, listen to me!
It's like all of my life, everyone has always told me,
여태까지 살아오면서
평생 모든 사람들이 저한테
'넌 신발이야. 넌 신발이야'
라고 말한 거에요
"you're a shoe! You're a shoe, you're a shoe, you're a shoe!"
오늘은 제가 갑자기 멈춰서서
'내가 신발이 되기 싫다면?'이라고 한거에요
And then today, I just stopped and I said,
"What if I don't want to be a shoe?
What if I want to be a-a purse?"
You know, or-or-or a hat?
'만약에 내가 손가방이 되고 싶거나,
모자가 되고 싶다면?'
모자 사달라는 말이 아니잖아요, 전..
No, I don't want you to buy me a hat.
아빤 비유법도 몰라요?!
it's a metaphor, daddy.
아빠를 설득하는 데서
어디서 문제가 있는지 알 수 있겠네
You can see where he'd have trouble.
아마 여기서 모니카하고
지내게 될 것 같아요
Well maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
그러면 이제는 누가 모니카랑 같이
사는지가 결정된 거나 마찬가지네
Well, I guess we've established who's staying here with Monica.
[Episode 118]
네 돈은 다 내 거다
각오해, 레이첼
Your money's mine, Green.
남대문 열렸다, 로스
Your fly is open, Geller.
내가 방금 뭘 알아냈는지 알아?
Oh, do you know what I just realized?
조커(joker)는 J로 시작하는
포커(poker)가 돼
"Joker" is "Poker" with a "J."
우연의 일치(coincidence) 아냐?
Coincidence?
그러고 보니까 그거는
C로 시작하는 'joincidence'가 되잖아
Hey, that's "joe-incidence" with a "C."
Ooh, look! Ugly naked guy lit a bunch of candles.
[Episode 107] 으, 저것 봐봐
벌거벗은 못난이가 촛불을 잔뜩 켰어
Ew!
aw...
진짜 아프겠는데
That had to hurt.
[Episode 309]
너희들도 추수감사절인데
Hey, it's your thanksgiving, too, you know?
미식축구만 보지 말고
좀 도와주지 그래?
Instead of watching football, you could help.
We know.
알았어
레이첼, 이 마쉬멜로우는
동심원 모양으로 배열해야 제대로야
Rachel, you want to put the marshmallows in concentric circles.
아니, 모니카
너만 그러길 바라지
No, mon, you want to put them in concentric circles.
내가 원하는 것은 이렇게 하는 거야
I want to do this.
한해도 안 걸러
Every year.
[Episode 508]
머리에 끼었어!
It's stuck!
조심해, 계단 있어
어쩌다 이랬어?
Well... step... how did it get on?!
챈들러 놀래킬려구 썼어!
I put it on to scare chandler.
맙소사, 모니카가 난리칠거야!
Oh, my god! Monica's going to totally freak out!
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
그리고 이 안에 냄새도 정말 나빠!
당연히 나쁘지, 죽은 동물
시체 안에 머리를 넣고 있는데
Yeah, of course it smells bad. You have your head inside a turkey's ass.
우.. 모니카다..
Oh, oh! Monica.
이제 칠면조 굽기 시작하..
세상에! 세상에!
Hey, did you get the turkey...?
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
저게 누구니?
Who is that?
조이야
It's Joey!
[Episode 412] 좋은 생각이 있어!
우리가 이기면 너희 수탉 없애
I got it. How 'bout, if we win, they have to get rid of the rooster?
Ooh, that's interesting.
그거 재밌겠다!
너희가 이기면..
If you win, we give up the bird.
그 녀석들 포기할게
대신 우리가 이기면...
but if we win... we get your apartment.
이 집 우리한테 넘겨
좋아!
Deal!
Wha...?
What?!
필드하키 골키퍼시절
모니카의 별명은?
What was Monica's nickname when she was a field hockey goalie?
- 뚱땡이 키퍼!
- 정답!
Big fat goalie.
Correct.
레이첼이 제일 좋아한다고 우기는
영화제목은?
Rachel claims this is her favorite movie.
- "위험한 관계"
- 정답!
Dangerous liaisons.
Correct.
하지만 실제로 제일 좋아하는 영화는?
Her actual favorite movie is?
- "공포의 주말"
- 정답!
Weekend at bernie'S.
Correct.
모니카는 수건을 여러 종류로 구분합니다
몇 가지로 구분할까요?
Monica categorizes her towels.
How many categories are there?
일상용.. 장식용..
Okay, everyday use.
Fancy. Guest. Fancy guest.
손님용.. 특별손님용..
- 2초 남았습니다
- 11개?
Two seconds. Ah... eleven?!
11개! 대단합니다!
정답입니다!
11, unbelievable.
11 is correct.
Yes!
챈들러가 맨 처음 여자의
가슴을 만진 나이는?
Chandler was how old when he first touched a girl's breast?
14살 때?
Fourteen?
- 아닙니다, 19살입니다
- 정말 고맙다
No, 19.
Thanks, man.
조이의 어릴 적
상상 속의 친구 이름은?
Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
His name was?
- 모리스!
- 정답! 그럼.. 직업은?
Maurice.
Correct.
His profession was...?
- 우주 카우보이!
- 정답!
Oh, space cowboy!
Correct.
챈들러의 직업은?
What is chandler bing's job?
10초 남았습니다
못 맞추면 남성팀이 이깁니다
Ten seconds. You need this, or you lose the game.
뭔가 옮기는 일인데..
it has something to do with transponding...
그래! 옮기.. 옮김사!
oh, oh, oh, he's a transpons...
transponster!
그건 단어도 아니야!
That's not even a word!
아는데.. 뭐지? 뭐야?
Oh!
No, I-I...
oh, my...
안돼!!!
noooooo...!
잘 들어! 너흰 정말 치사하게 구는
치사한 남자애들이야!
You know what?
You are mean boys who are just being mean.
Hey, don't get mad at us.
No one forced you to raise the stakes.
왜 우리한테 그래?
아무도 아파트를 걸라고 강요 안했어
아니야, 모니카가 나에게 강요했어!
모니카가 강요했다구!
That is not true.
She did.
She forced me.
네가 그 문제만 안틀렸어도
우린 여기서 살 수 있었어!
Hey, we'd still be living here,
if you hadn't gotten the question wrong.
Well, it was a stupid, unfair question.
문제가 공정하지도 않고
너무 유치했어!
내 문제를 탓하지마
Don't blame the questions.
왜 남의 집에서 악쓰고 그래?
너희가 이삿날 좋은 기분 망치잖아!
Would you all stop yelling in our apartment?
You are ruining moving day for us.
[Episode 515]
챈들러!
Chandler!
창문으로 네가 하는 짓 다 봤어!
I saw what you were doing through the window!
네가 내 동생한테 하는 짓 다 봤단 말야!
어서 이리 나와!
I saw what you were doing to my sister. Now, get out here!
도망 다닌 지 얼마나 됐지?
Listen, we had a good run.
You know, what was it?
4개월? 5개월?
Four-five months?
I mean, that's more than most people
have in a lifetime, so good-bye,
take care, bye-bye, then.
어떤 사람이 평생 살아도 못이룰
5개월의 사랑이었지, 그치? 그럼 잘 있어! 안녕!
무슨 일이야, 오빠?
Hey, Ross. What's up, bro?
What... the hell are you doing?!
대체 무슨 짓이야!
무슨 일이야?
Hey, wh-what's going on?
내 생각에는..
로스가 우리 사이 알게 된 것 같아
Well, I think-- I think--Ross knows about
me and monica.
임마! 로스 옆에 있잖아!
Dude, he's right there...
널 제일 친한 친구라고 믿었어!
얜 내 동생이란 말야!
I thought you were my best friend.
This is my sister.
내 친구랑 내 동생이 어떻게..
어떻게 이럴 수가 있어!
My best friend and my sister--
I-I cannot believe this.
희롱하거나 놀아나는 게 아냐
Look, we're not just messing around.
나 모니카 사랑해
네 동생 사랑한단 말야
I love her, okay?
I'm in love with her.
이런 식으로 오빠 알게 해서
정말 미안해
I am so sorry that you had to find out this way.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
I-I love him, too.
미안한데 사실이야
나도 챈들러 사랑해
내 친구랑 내 동생이?
My best friend and my sister!
믿어지지가 않아!
I cannot believe this!
[Episode 606]
이게 마지막 옷상자야
Well, this is the last box of your clothes.
여기다 이렇게 써 놓을게
"취향도 별나셔"
I'm just gonna label it "what were you thinking?"
재미있네, 난 복도 건너편으로 가서
챈들러에게 그 말을 써놓으려 했는데
Funny, 'cause I was just gonna go across the hall
and write that on Chandler.
저기 얘들아..
상황을 악화시키고 싶진 않지만..
Okay, you guys, I don't mean to make things worse,
but, um... I don't want to live with rachel anymore.
What?!
- 난 이제 레이첼이랑 같이 살기 싫어
- 뭐야?
너희 둘 정말 너무하잖아
You're just so mean to each other.
레이첼이랑 이렇게 헤어지는건 싫어
난 너 좋아한단 말야
And I don't want to end up like that with Rachel.
I still like you.
피비, 괜찮아
난 이사 안갈테니까
Well, phoebe, that's fine, because I'm not moving.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,whoa, whoa.
Phoebe, you gotta take her.
잠깐.. 피비, 얘 데려가야 해
내가 나쁜 말을 좀 했지만..
You know, I know I said some really bad stuff about her,
but you know, rachel does have some good qualities
that make her a good roommate.
레이첼도 룸메이트로서
좋은 점이 있긴 해
쟤는 카탈로그가 수없이 많고..
내가 좋아할만한건 접어서 표시해줘
She gets tons of catalogs.
And she'll fold down the pages of the things
that she thinks that I'd like.
또?
What else?
Well...
when I take a shower,
내가 샤워를 할때..
거울에 편지를 써놓곤 해
she leaves me little notes on the mirror.
응, 내가 좀 그래
Yeah, I do.
I do do that.
그건 좋네, 난 화장실에서
뭘 읽는 걸 좋아하거든
That's nice.
I like having things to read in the bathroom.
내가 소파에서 책 읽다가 잠이 들면..
When I fall asleep on the couch after reading,
이불을 덮어줘
she covers me over with a blanket.
그야.. 감기 걸리면 안되잖아
Well, you know, I don't want you to be cold.
그리고 내가 챈들러와
같이 살겠다고 말했을때
And... when I told her that I was going to be moving in with chandler,
적극적으로 밀어줬어
she was really supportive.
정말 고마웠어
You were so great.
덕분에 일이 쉬워졌었어
You made it so easy.
그런데 넌 떠나고..
And now you have to leave...
난 남자랑 살아야 해!
and I have to live with a boy!
안녕
Hey.
- 정말로 가버렸어
- 알아
She really left.
- 고마워
- 천만에, 룸메이트
Thank you.
No problem, roomie.
- 뭐 하나 물어봐도 돼?
- 물론
Can I ask you a question?
저 개가 대체 왜 여기 있는거야?
What the hell is that dog doing here?
[Episode 109]
자, 그럼 모두 건배합시다
Little toast here.
비록 모두의 계획이 계획대로 안되고
엉망진창이 되버렸지만
I know this isn't exactly the kind of thanksgiving
that all of you planned,
but for me, this has been really great, you know?
나한텐 멋진 추수감사절이야
이 자리엔 이혼이나 게워낸
음식 같은게 없기 때문인 것 같아
I think because it didn't involve divorce or projectile vomiting.
만약 누구는 스키타러 가버리고
누구는 가족들과 함께 지내고..
Anyway, I was just thinking, I mean, if you'd gone to vail,
or if you guys had been with your family,
or if you didn't have...syphilis and stuff...
또 누구는..
매독에 걸려버렸다면
우린 지금 함께 있지 못했을거야
...we wouldn't be all together, you know?
So, I guess what I'm trying to say is
그래서 난 너희들의 추수감사절이
엉망이 된 걸 감사드리고 싶어
that I'm very thankful that all of your
thanksgivings sucked.
- 감동적이었어
- 잘했어
That's so sweet.
Thank you...
자, 그럼 비참한 크리스마스를 위해!
And, hey, here's to a lousy christmas.
- 시시한 새해 첫날을 위해!
- 바로 그거야
And a crappy new year. Hear, hear!
너네 이사 가면 안돼
그냥 절대로 안돼
You can't move.
You just... you just can't.
레이첼 말이 맞아
여기야말로 너희가 있어야 할 곳이야
Rachel's right.
This is where you guys belong.
맞아, 누가 웨스트체스터에서
살고 싶어하겠어
Yeah, you don't want to live in westchester.
거기는 "체스터"로 끝나는 도시 중에
가장 나쁜 곳이야
That's like the worst of the chesters.
내가 가끔 내 아파트에서 혼자 있을 때
내가 창문 밖을 내다보면..
You know, sometimes,
when I'm alone in my apartment, I look over here,
너희가 저녁 먹고 있거나
TV 보고 있거나 그런데..
You guys are just having dinner or watching TV or something,but...
그것만으로도 기분이 좋아진단 말이야
It makes me feel better.
이제 내가 창문 밖을 내다보면 누굴 보겠어?
고트리브씨 가족? 양씨 가족?
And now when I look over, who am I gonna see?
The gottliebs? The yangs?
그 사람들을 보고 난 뒤의 기분은
별로 좋은 게 아니야
They don't make me feel so good.
맞아, 그러니까 이사하지 말고
계속 여기 있어
Yeah, so-so don't move, okay? Just stay here, and...
그리고 또 밤엔 커튼 좀 치고 말이야
Maybe close your blinds at night.
여보세요?
Hello?
낸시야
그쪽에서 우리 제안에 답신해왔어
It's nancy.
They responded to our offer.
어떻게 됐대?
And?
예, 감사합니다
Okay, thanks.
그들이 제안을 안받아들였어
They passed.
자신들이 부른 가격보다
1센트라도 적으면 안 된대
They said they wouldn't go a penny under the asking price.
- 우리도 그만큼은 돈이 없잖아
- 그러니까 말이야
We can't afford that.
I know.
그러면 결정이 났네
Well, there you go.
- 얘들아, 정말 미안해
- 나도 정말 유감이야
I'm really sorry, you guys. Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
창문으로 훔쳐보는 얘기를 한 후에야
전화가 온 게 사실 더 유감이지만..
I'm even more sorry that that phone call didn't come
before I told you about looking through the window.
이제 너희만의 시간을 갖도록
우리는 갈게
Yeah, well, we're going to let you be alone.
- 괜찮겠어?
- 응, 괜찮을거야
You going to be okay?
Yeah, we'll be okay.
너희를 사랑해
I love you guys.
Hey, you know,
I'm really sorry I wasn't more supportive before.
아까 너희 편 안들어준 것
정말 미안해
Oh, it's okay. We understand.
괜찮아, 우리도 이해해
Yeah, and about this nancy...
그리고 낸시에 관해서
물어볼 게 있는데
네가 같이 잘 것 아니라면
내가 자도 괜찮을까?
if you're not sleeping with her, should I?
물론 다른 집 중에도
좋은 것이 많겠지만..
I know there'll be other houses, but I just...
- 정말 멋진 집이였는데
- 그러게..
I love that one so much.
Yeah.
그럼 우리가 그 집 샀으니까
잘된 거네
Well, it's a good thing we got it, then.
- 뭐라고?
- 우리가 그 집 샀어!
What?!
We got the house!
오 세상에!
Oh, my god!
얘들 앞에서 말할 수가 없었어
I just didn't want to tell you in front of them.
- 맙소사! 우리가 그 집 샀단 말이야?
- 우리가 집을 샀어!
Oh, my god! We got it?
We got the house?!
We are getting the house. We are getting a house
우리 집 생겼어
아이도 얻었고..
and a baby,
우리 어른이 돼가고 있어
We are growing up.
확실히 그런 것 같아
We sure are.
그러면 쟤네한테는 누가 말하지?
So who is gonna tell them?
- 나는 안 해!
- 나도 안 해! 젠장!
Not it! / Not it!
Damn it!
레이첼.. 이건 내꺼야
And rachel, this is yours.
What are these for?! You'll see.
- 그런데 이 선물은 왜 주는 거야?
- 보면 알아
- 얘들아 모두 자기 것 뜯어봐
- 알았어
All right. Everybody, open them.
oh, wow, this is so beautiful!
이거 정말 예쁘다!
Oh, these are the ones I was looking at in the store.
I know.
- 내가 가게에서 봐둔건데
- 그래, 바로 그거야
I love this.
이거 엄청 좋다!
고기가 든 샌드위치다!
A meatball sub!?
고마워!
Thanks!
근데 정말 이게 다 뭐야?
Seriously, you guys. What's going on?
What are these for?
전에는 어떻게 말할 지 몰랐는데..
Well, I didn't know how to tell you before, but...
- 우리 그 집 샀어
- 선물 즐겨!
we got the house.
Enjoy!
쟤네가 뭐래?
What did they say?